<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="tAndC_title">Term and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tAndC_description">All full version documents listed in this application are password protected and member’s only. We recommend a new subscriber should read the sample procedures and overview contents carefully and make an informed decision about the suitability before attempting to purchase the subscription. The sample procedures are smaller than their full versions and listed on the home screen under “Sample Content” icon. No procedure listed in this application provides misleading or false information intentionally and can be useful when applied correctly. We expect readers will understand the principles and concepts outlined in the published documents and rewrite their own version.</string>
    <string name="tAndC_paymentOptions">Payment Options</string>
    <string name="tAndC_paymentOptionsDes">All payments are securely processed through In App Purchase facility. The payments could incur only if the user would made an informed decision to upgrade their free accounts to paid subscription. At the time of creating subscription accounts user will create a set of user ID and Password. User can change the Password as many times as they want through the “Profile” option. ID and Passwords will be deactivated by the application administrator subject to cancellation of a subscription.</string>
    <string name="tAndC_copyright">Copyright</string>
    <string name="tAndC_copyrightDes">All documents are Copyright protected. Copying or editing documents are prohibited and may not be possible. Illegal copying and using of full or part of the information published in this site for other commercial purposes is completely prohibited. Site authority keeps all rights for the use of its services and may take any legal actions if found an unauthorized use of any of its publications. The information contained in this site is designed to provide accurate and authoritative information regarding the subjects addressed. Purchase of subscription does not transfer ownership of any part of the documents listed in this site.</string>
    <string name="tAndC_pricesAndCancellation">Prices and cancellation</string>
    <string name="tAndC_pricesAndCancellationDes">New subscription prices and trial periods are subject to variation from time to time as per the discretion of application administration team. However, existing subscription does not change until the end of the subscription. \n\nSubscriber holds the right to cancel a subscription at any time without prior notice. New subscription price will apply if re-subscribed unless otherwise agreed by the application Administrator. The Administratorreserves the right to cancel a subscription if such a necessity arises without prior notice. Application Administratoris not liable to make a refund anytime a subscription is cancelled by either party.
</string>

</resources>